greybox.com 2015-09-20

# Welcome to Grey Box!

## PRIVACY POLICY

_Effective Date: March 11, 2014._

## Introduction

Welcome! You have arrived at [www.greybox.com](http://www.greybox.com/) and/or are otherwise interacting with our Service (defined below), which is owned and operated by Redux! Games, LLC d/b/a Grey Box ( **“Grey Box" or “we,“our" or “us"** ). This **“Privacy Policy"** governs your use of any online service location (e.g., web site or mobile app) that posts a link to this Privacy Policy (each a **“Site"** ) (including, without limitation, both mobile and online versions), operated by or at the direction of Grey Box, and also applies to your use of games, online games, including social games and the online features of games, other interactive features, widgets, plug-ins, applications, content, downloads and/or other services that we own and control and make available through a Site and/or that posts a link to this Privacy Policy (collectively, the **“Service"** ), regardless of how you access or use them, whether via personal computers, mobile devices or otherwise, but does not apply to data we receive from third parties, unless we combine such data with Personal Information (defined below) that we have ourselves collected under this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy does **not** apply to our data collection activities offline or otherwise outside of our Service (unless otherwise stated below), and does not govern the data practices of third parties that may interact with our Service. 

To the extent we provide you notice on our Service of different or additional privacy policies or practices (e.g., at the point of our collection), those additional terms shall govern such data collection and use.

In addition, please review the Service's [Terms of Service](http://www.greybox.com/terms-of-service/), which governs your use of the Service. 

_By using our Service, you consent to our Privacy Policy and Terms of Service and our collection, use and sharing of your information and data, and other activities, as described below._

## Linkable Table of Contents

It is important that you read and understand the entire Privacy Policy before using the Service. To ease review, each section below contains a brief introductory summary and a link to the full explanation. Click on the headings and the “More" buttons to be taken to the full explanation. Any capitalized terms that appear in but are not otherwise defined in the introduction have the meanings given to them elsewhere in the Privacy Policy. 

**1\. What Information Does the Service Collect?**

We collect and receive certain information about you as you interact with our Service, explained further in this section. More

**(a) Information You Provide to Us**

We may collect certain Personal Information and Demographic Information that you provide to us when you interact with the Service. For example, we may collect this information through various forms and in various places on the Service, including newsletter registration forms, through “contact us" forms, or when you otherwise interact with the Service. More

**(b) Information Collected and Stored As You Access and Use the Service**

Certain information may be collected from you automatically when you access and use the Service. For example, we and third parties may use Tracking Technologies to collect Usage Information based on your Device Identifier for a variety of purposes, including tracking, targeting, and advertising, which may include activities across time and third party locations. We do not look for or respond to do not track signals, but you may have certain other options regarding tracking and/or targeting. This Section provides details on: • Usage Information • Tracking Technologies • Tracking Technologies Usage • Tracking Technologies Choices and Consent • Third Party Tracking and Do Not Track

More

**(c) Information Third Parties Provide About You**

We may obtain information about you from third parties. More

**(d) Interactions with Third-Party Services**

If you interact with third-party services, such as using Facebook Connect to log in, those services may send us information about you and you or we may send them information about you. More

**(e) Information You Provide About a Third Party**

You may provide us information about others, such as when you send a friend a message. If so, the information you provide (names, e-mail addresses, etc.) may be used to facilitate the communication, but will not be used for other marketing purposes unless your friend consents. You may be identified to the friend in connection with such a message. More

**2\. How Do We Use The Information Collected?**

We use your Personal Information, Demographic Information and Usage Information for a variety of purposes detailed in this section including:

• Generally • Location-based Services • Contact Us • Use of Information For Recruitment Purposes

More

**3\. How and When Do We Share Information With Third Parties?**

We may provide your information to third parties under various circumstances detailed in this section. These may include:

**(a) When You Request Information From or Provide Information to Third Parties**

If you request information from third parties, request that we send information to third parties or interact with third-party services, content, ads or tools (including Facebook and other third party share functionality) we may share your information with such parties and/or they may collect your information directly. This may also include ordering or purchasing products from third parties through us where we indicate that the third party rather than us is the seller. More

**(b) Third Parties Providing Services on Our Behalf**

Our vendors may collect your information on our behalf or we may share it with them so that they may provide services to us and you. Some may offer you choices regarding the collection and use of your information. More

**(c) To Deliver Social Content and Advertising**

We may share or transfer your content and information in connection with our social media features and/or social advertising, which may specifically identify you and your activities (e.g., John watched this video, Julie likes Grey Box) to people associated with you (such as members of your social networks). However, you have the opportunity to exercise certain opt-out options. More

**(d) To Protect the Rights of Grey Box and Others**

There are a variety of administrative and legal reasons for which we may share some or all of your information. More

**(e) Affiliates and Business Transfer**

We may share your information with our affiliates or in the event of a sale, merger or similar transaction. More

**(f) Co-Branded Areas**

Co-branded areas may include information collection by us and third parties. Such third parties' privacy policies, not ours, govern their practices. More

**(g) Sweepstakes, Contests And Promotions**

Promotions entrants may be required to consent to certain information sharing. More

**(h) EEOC/Affirmative Action Reporting**

Certain employment application, self-identifying information (e.g., race and gender) may be shared with the government and other third parties. More

**(i) Your California Privacy Rights**

We do not share your Personal Information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes without giving you the choice to opt-in or opt-out of such sharing. More

**(j) Your European Privacy Rights**

Certain European residents have certain data protection rights. More

**4\. What About Information I Disclose Publicly or to Others?**

**(a) User-Generated Content and Public Information**

Posting content in public areas makes it available to others. We may share and use your public information for any reason not otherwise prohibited by this Privacy Policy. More

**(b) Name and Likeness**

You grant us the right to use your name and likeness in connection with your posting and activities. More

**(c) Profiles** Learn more about Profile settings. More

**5\. Do Third-Party Content, Links to Third-Party Sites and/or Third-Party Apps Appear on the Service?**

We may allow you to access third-party content on the Service, or to link to third-party applications and locations from the Service, but we are not responsible for your interaction with third-party content, apps, and locations. More

**6\. Are Ads Served On the Service?**

No, but third parties may send you targeted ads based on your location, information and/or behavior. If you object, do not use our Service and/or exercise choices some third parties may offer. More

**7\. How Do I Change My Information And Communications Preferences?**

You may change certain account information and communications preferences as more fully detailed in this section. More

**8\. What About Transfer of Information to the United States?**

You consent to your data being transferred to the United States, which has different data protection laws than other countries. More

**9\. What Should Parents Know About Children?**

We do not intend to collect Personal Information from children. If you think we have, let us know. More

**10\. What About Security?**

No data security is absolute, but we endeavor to take reasonable steps to secure data appropriately. More

**11\. What About Changes to the Privacy Policy?**

We may change this Privacy Policy upon posting of a revised Privacy Policy. However, we will continue to treat your Personal Information under the terms of the privacy policy in effect when it was collected unless you otherwise consent. More

### The Full Detailed Privacy Policy

**1\. What Information Does the Service Collect?**

**(a) Information You Provide to Us** **Personal Information and Demographic Information.** On the Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain categories of information such as: (1) personally identifiable information, which is information that identifies you personally, such as your first and/or last name, e-mail address, and home address ( **“Personal Information"** ); and (2) demographic information, such as information about your gender, your type of business, age, marital status, income or revenues, education level, and occupation ( **“Demographic Information"** ). We may collect this information through various forms and in various places on the Service, including account registration forms, contact us forms, or when you otherwise interact with the Service. To the extent we combine Demographic Information with your Personal Information we collect directly from you on the Service, we will treat the combined data as Personal Information under this Privacy Policy. 

**(b) Information Collected or Stored As You Access and Use the Service**

In addition to any Personal Information or other information that you choose to submit to us via our Service, we and our third-party service providers may use a variety of technologies that automatically (or passively) store or collect certain information whenever you visit or interact with the Service ( **“Usage Information"** ). This Usage Information may be stored or accessed using a variety of technologies that may be downloaded to your personal computer, browser, laptop, tablet, mobile phone or other device (a “Device") whenever you visit or interact with our Service. To the extent we associate Usage Information with your Personal Information we collect directly from you on the Service, we will treat it as Personal Information. 

This Usage Information may include:

• your IP address, UDID or other unique identifier ( _“Device Identifier"_ ). A Device Identifier is a number that is automatically assigned to your Device used to access the Service, and our computers identify your Device by its Device Identifier;

• your Device functionality (including browser, operating system, hardware, mobile network information);

• the URL that referred you to our Service;

• the areas within our Service that you visit and your activities there, including remembering you and your preferences;

• your Device location;

• your Device characteristics; and

• certain other Device data, including the time of day, among other information. 

**Tracking Technologies.** We may use various methods and technologies to store or collect Usage Information ( **“Tracking Technologies"** ). Tracking Technologies may set, change, alter or modify settings or configurations on your Device. A few of the Tracking Technologies include, without limitation, the following (and subsequent technology and methods later developed):

**Cookies.** A cookie is a data file placed on a Device when it is used to visit the Service. A Flash cookie (or locally shared object) is a data file placed on a Device via the Adobe Flash plug-in that may be built-in to or downloaded by you to your Device. HTML5 cookies can be programmed through HTML5 local storage.

**Web Beacons.** Small graphic images or other web programming code called web beacons (also known as “1x1 GIFs" or “clear GIFs") may be included in our Service's pages and messages. Web beacons may be invisible to you, but any electronic image or other web programming code inserted into a page or e-mail can act as a web beacon. Web beacons or similar technologies may be used for a number of purposes, including, without limitation, to count visitors to the Service, to monitor how users navigate the Service, to count how many e-mails that were sent were actually opened or to count how many particular articles or links were actually viewed. 

**Embedded Scripts.** An embedded script is programming code that is designed to collect information about your interactions with the Service, such as the links you click on. The code is temporarily downloaded onto your Device from our web server or a third party service provider, is active only while you are connected to the Service, and is deactivated or deleted thereafter. 

**Browser Fingerprinting.** Collection and analysis of information from your Device, such as, without limitation, your operating system, plug-ins, system fonts and other data, for purposes of identification.  
ETag, or Entity Tag. A feature of the cache in browsers. It is an opaque identifier assigned by a web server to a specific version of a resource found at a URL. If the resource content at that URL ever changes, a new and different ETag is assigned. Used in this manner ETags are a form of Device Identifier. ETag tracking may generate unique tracking values even where the consumer blocks HTTP, Flash, and/or HTML5 cookies. 

**Recognition Technologies.** Technologies, including application of statistical probability to data sets, which attempt to recognize or make assumptions about users and devices (e.g., that a user of multiple devices in the same user).

**Location-identifying Technologies.** Additionally, the Services may use GPS (global positioning systems) software and other location-based technologies such as iBeacons to locate you so we may verify your location, deliver you relevant content based on your location, as well as allow you to share your location to other users as part of the services we provide via the Services. Upon downloading the App, we provide location-based services to your approximate and/or exact location information. In addition, to traditional GPS location-based services, some of the retailers and others we work with may install low power Bluetooth, wifi, radio transmitters, or other devices in physical locations, which emit a signal that the App can detect to pinpoint your location or otherwise interact with the App ( **“iBeacons"** ). Because iBeacons are more precise than GPS, we can improve the Services such as to send you more specific and relevant messages and offers. In addition, you may be able to send your location information via the Services to other Services users. You should consider the pros and cons involved in disclosing your location information to us and to other people. Where a user of the Services requests that their location information be revealed to other persons, the user will be provided options for managing sharing services, which may be through third party services such as through Twitter and Facebook. We are not responsible for the acts, omissions or policies of such third parties.

**Tracking Technologies Usage.** We may use Tracking Technologies for a variety of purposes, including:

_Strictly Necessary._ We may use cookies or other Tracking Technologies that we consider are strictly necessary to allow you to use and access our Service, including cookies required to prevent fraudulent activity, improve security or allow you to make use of shopping cart functionality. 

_Performance Related._ We may use cookies or other Tracking Technologies that are useful in order to assess the performance of the Service, including as part of our analytic practices or otherwise to improve the content, products or services offered through the Service. 

_Functionality Related._ We may use cookies or other Tracking Technologies that are required to offer you enhanced functionality when accessing the Service, including identifying you when you sign in to our Service or keeping track of our specified preferences, including in terms of the presentation of content on our Service. 

_Targeting Related._ We may use Tracking Technologies to deliver content, including ads, relevant to your interests on our Service and third party sites based on how you interact with our advertisements or content. This includes using Tracking Technologies to understand the usefulness to you of the advertisements and content that may be delivered to you. Further information on this, and your opt-out choices, is found in Section 6 below. 

_Tracking Technologies Choices and Consent._

We obtain your consent to our information storage or collection Tracking Technologies by providing you with transparent information in our Privacy Policy and providing you with the opportunity to make a choice to disable cookies as set forth below. Please note that we are not required to obtain your consent to the information collection Tracking Technologies identified above that are strictly necessary. If you are a resident of Europe, you may have the right to object to other use of information storage or collection technologies – further information on this right for marketing-related purposes is found in Section 3 (j) below.

**Third Party Tracking and Do Not Track.**

There may be other Tracking Technologies now and later devised and used by us in connection with the Service. Further, third parties may use Tracking Technologies in connection with our Service, which may include the collection of information about your online activities over time and across third-party web sites or online services. We may not control those Tracking Technologies and we are not responsible for them. However, you consent to potentially encountering third party Tracking Technologies in connection with use of our Service and accept that our statements under this Privacy Policy do not apply to the Tracking Technologies or practices of such third parties. For more information on our vendors, and their Tracking Technologies, click here. For more information on advertising and advertisers, and related Tracking Technologies, click here. Also, various third parties are developing or have developed signals or other mechanisms for the expression of consumer choice regarding the collection of information about an individual consumer's online activities over time and across third-party web sites or online services (e.g., browser do not track signals). Currently, we do not monitor or take any action with respect to these signals or other mechanisms. For more information on third party programs that may permit you to exercise choice regarding targeted advertising based on such information, click here. For more information on our vendors, click here.

Regular cookies may generally be disabled or removed by tools that are available as part of most commercial browsers, and in some but not all instances can be blocked in the future by selecting certain settings. Each browser you use will need to be set separately and different browsers offer different functionality and options in this regard. Also, these tools may not be effective with regard to Flash cookies or HTML5 cookies or other Tracking Technologies. For information on disabling Flash cookies go to Adobe's website [www.adobe.com](http://www.adobe.com/). Please be aware that if you disable or remove these technologies some parts of our Services may not work and that when you revisit our Services your ability to limit browser-based Tracking Technologies is subject to your browser settings and limitations. Further, App-related Tracking Technologies in connection with non-browser usage (e.g., most functionality of the App) can only be disabled by uninstalling the App. To uninstall an app, follow the instructions from your operating system or handset manufacturer.

**(c) Information Third Parties Provide About You** We may receive information about you from your friends and others that use the Service, such as when they submit content to us or post on the Service. Additionally, we may, from time to time, supplement the information we collect directly from you on our Service with outside records from third parties for various purposes, including to enhance our ability to serve you, to tailor our content to you and to offer you opportunities that may be of interest to you. To the extent we combine information we receive from those sources with your Personal Information we collect on the Service, it will be treated as Personal Information and we will apply this Privacy Policy to such combined information, unless we have disclosed otherwise. In no other circumstances do our statements under this Privacy Policy apply to information we receive about you from third parties. 

**(d) Interactions with Third-Party Services** The Service may include functionality that allows certain kinds of interactions between the Service and a third-party web site or application. The use of this functionality may involve the third-party operator providing certain information, including Personal Information, to us. For example, when you register with the Service, you may have an option to use your Facebook, Google or other account provided by a third-party site or application to facilitate the registration and log-in or transaction process on the Service, or otherwise link accounts. If we offer and you choose to use this functionality to access or use our Service, the third-party site or application may send Personal Information about you to us. If so, we will then treat it as Personal Information under this Privacy Policy, since we are collecting it as a result of your accessing of and interaction on our Service. In addition, we may provide third-party sites' interfaces or links on the Service to facilitate your sending a communication from the Service. For example, we may use third parties to facilitate emails, tweets or Facebook postings. These third parties may retain any information used or provided in any such communications or other activities and these third parties' practices are not subject to our Privacy Policy. Grey Box may not control or have access to your communications through these third parties. Further, when you use third-party sites or services, you are using their services and not our services and they, not we, are responsible for their practices. You should review the applicable third-party privacy policies before using such third-party tools on our Service. 

**(e) Information You Provide About a Third Party** You may send someone else a communication from the Service, such as sending an invitation to a friend. If so, the information you provide (names, e-mail addresses, etc.) is used to facilitate the communication and is not used by us for any other marketing purpose unless we obtain consent from that person or we explicitly say otherwise. Please be aware that when you use any send-to-a-friend functionality on our Service, your contact information, name or user name and message may be included in the communication sent to your addressee(s). Some of these tools may be third-party tools subject to third-party privacy policies as further detailed in Section 1(d) and Section 5. 

Return to policy summary and navigation

**2\. How Do We Use the Information Collected?**

_Generally._ We may use your Personal Information, Demographic Information or Usage Information that we collect about you: (1) to provide you with information or services or process transactions that you have requested or agreed to receive, including to send you electronic newsletters, or to provide you with special offers or promotional materials on behalf of us or third parties; (2) to enable you to participate in a variety of the Services' features such as online entry sweepstakes, contests or other promotion; (3) to process your registration with any of the Services, including verifying your information is active and valid; (4) to improve the Services or create new service offerings, to customize your experience on any of the Services, or to serve you specific content that is most relevant to you; (5) to contact you with regard to your use of any of the Services and, in our discretion, changes to the any of the Services and/or any of the Services' policies; (6) for internal business purposes; and (7) for purposes disclosed at the time you provide your information or as otherwise set forth in this Privacy Policy.

_Interest-Based Advertising and Location-Based Services._ We may also use your Personal Information, Demographic Information or Usage Information that we collect about you: (1) to specifically target relevant advertisements or content to you based on how you interact with our Services; (2) to understand the usefulness to you of the advertisements or content that have been delivered to you; and (3) to increase our Services profile, including allowing you to comment or add content to the Services. Further, we may use your location information (including proximity to Tracking Technologies existing the physical world that the App interacts with, for example iBeacons in a retail store) such as to display nearby businesses and offers, or to enable or verify certain actions.

_Contact Us._ Please note that information submitted to any of the Services via a “contact us" or other similar customer inquiry function may not receive a response. We will not use the information provided by you in a customer inquiry communication to contact you for marketing purposes unrelated to your request unless you agree otherwise. 

_Use of Information for Recruitment Purposes._ Where you have provided us with Personal Information or Demographic Information as part of an online application for employment or internship, we may use that information in order to allow us to make an informed decision about whether to proceed with your application. We may, as part of this recruitment process, collect information about your education, employment history and similar matters. Where this Personal Information or Demographic Information is considered to be sensitive, you expressly consent to our processing of this information for recruitment purposes by submitting it to us. 

Return to policy summary and navigation

**3\. How and When Do We Share Information with Third Parties?**

We may share non-Personal Information, such as aggregated user statistics, with third parties. We may share your Device Identifiers with third parties along with data related to you and your activities. We do not share your Personal Information that we have collected directly from you on our Service with third parties for those third parties' direct marketing purposes unless we have given you the choice to consent or withhold consent to such sharing at the time you provide your Personal Information, in which case we will honor your choice such as signing up for their email list or connecting via a social media platform such as Facebook or Twitter. If we de-identify data about you, it is not treated as Personal Information by us, and we may share it with others freely. In addition, we may share the information we have collected about you, including Personal Information, as disclosed at the time you provide your information and as described below or otherwise in this Privacy Policy. Company may disclose your information as follows:

**(a) When You Request Information From or Provide Information to Third Parties.** You may be presented with an option on our Service to receive certain information and/or marketing offers directly from third parties or to have us send certain information to third parties or give them access to it. If you choose to do so, your Personal Information and other information may be disclosed to such third parties and all information you disclose will be subject to the third-party privacy policies and practices of such third parties. In addition, third parties may store, collect or otherwise have access to your information when you interact with their Tracking Technologies, content, tools apps or ads on our Service or link to them from our Service. This may include using third-party tools such as Facebook, Twitter, Pinterest or other third-party posting or content sharing tools and by so interacting you consent to such third party practices. It may also include ordering or purchasing products from third parties through us where we indicate that the third party rather than us is the seller. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and practices of such third parties and, therefore, you should review such third-party privacy policies and practices of such third parties prior to requesting information from or otherwise interacting with them. 

**(b) Third Parties Providing Services on Our Behalf.** We may use third-party vendors to perform certain services on behalf of us or the Service, such as hosting the Service, designing and/or operating the Service's features, tracking the Service's activities and analytics, and enabling us to send you special offers or perform other administrative services. We may provide these vendors with access to user information, including Device Identifiers and Personal Information, to carry out the services they are performing for you or for us. Third-party analytics and other service providers may set and access their own Tracking Technologies on your Device and they may otherwise collect or have access to information about you, potentially including Personal Information, about you. We are not responsible for those third party technologies or activities arising out of them. However, some may offer you certain choices regarding their practices, and information we have been informed of regarding such choices is available. We are not responsible for the effectiveness of or compliance with any third parties' opt-out options. 

**(c) To Deliver Social Content and Advertising.** We, and others we work with (e.g., third party publishers, advertisers and advertising services providers) may use your Personal Information, Demographic Information and/or Usage Information we have collected in connection with the Service to target and deliver content and advertisements to you and other users, both on and off of our Service. We may, from time to time, offer you options to manage this type of social sharing via your Profile settings, and we will, make reasonable good faith efforts to respect settings. However, we do not guarantee that your setting selections will be effective immediately or be error free when delivering social content and advertisements. For more information on these setting options, or to let us know about any problems regarding such settings, visit [here](http://greybox.com/account-settings/)

**(d) To Protect the Rights of Grey Box and Others.** To the fullest extent permitted by applicable law, we may also disclose your information if we believe in good faith that doing so is necessary or appropriate to: (i) protect or defend the rights, safety or property of Grey Box or third parties (including through the enforcement of this Policy, our [Terms of Service](http://www.greybox.com/terms-of-service/), and other applicable agreements and policies); or (ii) comply with legal and regulatory obligations (e.g., pursuant to law enforcement inquiries, subpoenas or court orders). To the fullest extent permitted by applicable law, we have complete discretion in electing to make or not make such disclosures, and to contest or not contest requests for such disclosures, all without notice to you. 

**(e) Affiliates and Business Transfer.** We may share your information, including your Device Identifiers and Personal Information, Demographic Information and Usage Information with our parent, subsidiaries and affiliates ( **“Affiliates"** ). We also reserve the right to disclose and transfer all such information: (i) to a subsequent owner, co-owner or operator of the Service or applicable database; or (ii) in connection with a merger, consolidation, restructuring, the sale of substantially all of our interests and/or assets or other corporate change, including, during the course of any due diligence process.

**(f) Co-Branded Areas.** Certain areas of the Service may be provided to you in association with third parties (* _“Co-Branded Areas"_ ) such as sponsors, charities and political organizations and may require you to disclose Personal Information to them. Such Co-Branded Areas will identify the third party and indicate if they have a privacy policy that applies to their collection and use of you information. If you elect to register for products and/or services, communicate with such third parties or download their content or applications, at Co-Branded Areas, you may be providing your information to both us and the third party. Further, if you sign-in to a Co-Branded Area with a username and password obtained on the Service, your Personal Information may be disclosed to the identified third parties for that Co-Branded Area. We are not responsible for such third party's data collection or practices and you should look to such third party privacy policies for more information. 

**(g) Sweepstakes, Contests and Promotions.** We may offer sweepstakes, contests, and other promotions (any, a **“Promotion"** ) through the Service that may require registration. By participating in a Promotion, you are agreeing to official rules that govern that Promotion, which may contain specific requirements of you, including, allowing the sponsor of the Promotion to use your name, voice and/or likeness in advertising or marketing associated with the Promotion. If you choose to enter a Promotion, Personal Information may be disclosed to third parties or the public in connection with the administration of such Promotion, including, in connection with winner selection, prize fulfillment, and as required by law or permitted by the Promotion's official rules, such as on a winners list. 

**(h) EEOC / Affirmative Action Reporting.** In conjunction with laws and regulations enforced by the Equal Employment Opportunity Commission ( **“EEOC"** ), the Office of Federal Contract Compliance Programs ( **“OFCCP"** ) and similar state and local regulatory agencies, we may ask you to provide us with self-identifying information (such as veteran status, gender and ethnicity). If requested, providing such self-identifying information is voluntary, but if you do provide us with such information, we may submit that information, to the EEOC, the OFCCP and similar state and local regulatory agencies or otherwise use or disclose it for business-related purposes, including, without limitation, responding to information requests, fulfilling regulatory reporting requirements and defending against employment related complaints. 

**(i) Your California Privacy Rights.** We may from time to time elect to share certain information about you collected by us on the Service with third parties for those third parties' direct marketing purposes. California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits California residents who have supplied personal information, as defined in the statute, to us to, under certain circumstances, [to request and obtain certain information regarding our disclosure, if any, of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. If this applies, you may obtain the categories of personal information shared and the names and addresses of all third parties that received personal information for their direct marketing purposes during the immediately prior calendar year (e.g. requests made in 2014 will receive information about 2013 sharing activities). To make such a request, please provide sufficient information for us to determine if this applies to you, attest to the fact that you are a California resident and provide a current California address for our response. You may make this request in writing at: Attn: Legal Department, Grey Box, 1100 Louisiana Street, 52nd Floor, Houston, TX 77002. 

**(j) Your European Privacy Rights.** If you are a resident of Europe, including Switzerland, you may have the right to ask us not to process certain of your personal data (or provide it to third parties to process) for marketing purposes. You can exercise your right, if applicable, to prevent such processing at any time by contacting us in the following ways: Postal Mail: Attn: Legal Department, Grey Box, 1100 Louisiana Street, 52nd Floor, Houston, TX 77002; By e-mail: [www.greybox.com/support/contact/](http://www.greybox.com/support/contact/)

Return to policy summary and navigation

**4\. What About Information I Disclose Publicly Or To Others?**

**(a) User-Generated Content and Public Information.** The Service may permit you to submit ideas, photographs, user profiles, writings, music, video, audio recordings, computer graphics, pictures, data, questions, comments, suggestions or other content, including Personal Information (collectively, “User Content"), such as on blogs and message boards. We or others may store, display, reproduce, publish, distribute or otherwise use User Content online or offline in any media or format (currently existing or hereafter developed) and may or may not attribute it to you. Others may have access to this User Content and may have the ability to share it with third parties. Please think carefully before deciding what information you share, including Personal Information, in connection with your User Content. Please note that Company does not control who will have access to the information that you choose to make public, and cannot ensure that parties who have access to such publicly available information will respect your privacy or keep it secure. We are not responsible for the privacy or security of any information that you make publicly available on the Service or what others do with information you share with them on the Service. We are not responsible for the accuracy, use or misuse of any User Content that you disclose or receive from third parties through the Service. 

**(b) Name and Likeness.** We may also publish your name, voice, likeness and other Personal Information that is part of your User Content, and we may use the content, or any portion of the content, for advertising, marketing, publicity and promotional activities. This includes use in connection with social content ads as more fully explained in Section 3(c). For full terms and conditions regarding User Content you submit to the Service, please review our [Terms of Service](http://www.greybox.com/terms-of-service). 

**(c) Profiles.** A user's profile page may be, by default, set up to display information such as the user's display name, images, location (city/state/country), groups that the user has joined and optional information added by the user including, for example, the user's display name, tagline, avatars, photographs, and screenshots, etc. We may make it possible for users to see a report on other users that visited a profile page and this gives users access to such visitor's profile pages. Profile information is used by us primarily to be presented back to and edited by you when you access the Service and to be presented to others permitted to view that information on the Service. In some cases (e.g., posting to your page), other users of the Service may be able to supplement your profile. We may offer users the ability to manage their public profile and use profile preference settings as explained at Profile Preferences, the functionality and features of which are subject to change from time-to-time so visit it frequently to confirm the settings reflect your then current preferences and we recommend that you do not post information or content as part of your profile that you are not prepared to make public. Changing setting options may not result in immediate changes to the settings, which are subject to our operations and maintenance schedules. Users should carefully consider the use of such settings to improve information display options and to ensure the settings are properly set and functioning in the manner desired. Notwithstanding the availability of profile preference settings, you should be aware that these settings are for convenience only, do not employ complex data security protection and may not be error free. Further, other users that have access may repost or otherwise make public your information or content. Accordingly, discretion and good judgment should be exercised when posting information or content as part of your profile. 

Return to policy summary and navigation

**5\. Do Third-Party Content, Links To Third-Party Sites, and/or Third-Party Apps Appear on the Service?** The Service may contain content that is supplied by a third party, and those third parties may collect Usage Information and your Device Identifier when pages from the Service are served to you. In addition, when you are on the Service you may be directed to other services that are operated and controlled by third parties that we do not control. We are not responsible for the data collection and privacy practices employed by any of these third parties or their services and they may be tracking you across multiple sites and may be sharing the results of that tracking with us and/or others. For example, if you “click" on a link, the “click" may take you off the Service onto a different site. These other sites may associate their Tracking Technologies with you, independently collect data about you, including Personal Information, and may or may not have their own published privacy policies. 

Third-party applications may also be available via the Service. The owners of these applications ( **“Third-Party Owners"** ) may collect Personal Information and other data from you and may have their own policies and practices. We are not responsible for how Third-Party Owners or their applications collect or use your information and they may be tracking you across multiple sites and may be sharing the results of that tracking with us and/or others. These Third-Party Owners may have their own terms of service, privacy policies or other policies and ask you to agree to the same. We are not responsible for these third-party privacy policies or the practices of Third-Party Owners. Be sure to review any available policies before submitting any personally identifiable information to a third-party application or otherwise interacting with it and exercise caution in connection with these applications. We also encourage you to note when you leave our Service and to review the third-party privacy policies of all third-party locations and exercise caution in connection with them. 

Return to policy summary and navigation

**6\. Are Ads Served On the Service?**

The Service does not use third parties such as network advertisers and ad exchanges to serve advertisements on the Service.

The Service may use third-party analytics and other service providers to evaluate and provide us and/or third parties with information about the use of the Service and viewing of our content. Network advertisers are third parties that display advertisements, which may be based on your visits to the Service and other apps and sites you have visited. Third-party ad serving enables advertisers to target advertisements to you for products and services in which you might be interested. 

The Service's third-party exchange providers, the advertisers, the sponsors and/or traffic measurement services may themselves set and access their own cookies (including Flash cookies), web beacons and other Tracking Technologies on your Device and track certain behavioral Usage Information regarding users of your Device via a Device Identifier. These third-party Tracking Technologies may be set to, among other things: (a) help deliver advertisements to you that you might be interested in; (b) prevent you from seeing the same advertisements too many times; and (c) understand the usefulness to you of the advertisements that have been delivered to you. You acknowledge and agree that associated technology may access and use your Device and may set or change settings on your Device in connection with the associated operations. Note that any images (or any other parts of content) served by third parties in association with third-party ads or other content may serve as web beacons, which enable third parties to carry out the previously described activities. 

Third-party Tracking Technologies are not controlled by us, even if they use our technology to help store or collect data. Statements regarding our practices do not apply to the methods for collecting information used by these third-party advertisers and others or the use of the information that such third parties collect. We do however work with third parties to make efforts to have you provided with information on their practices and any available opportunity to exercise choice. The relevant third party's terms of service, privacy policy, permissions, notices and choices should be reviewed regarding their collection, storage and sharing practices. We make no representations regarding the policies or practices of third-party advertisers or advertising networks or exchanges or related third parties. 

However, some may offer you certain choices regarding their practices, and information we have been informed of regarding such choices is available here. Further, while we do not currently serve advertisements on the Service, you may wish to visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp>, which provides information regarding this practice by Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI") members, and your choices regarding having this information used by these companies, including the “opt-out" procedures of NAI members. Opting out of one or more NAI members only means that those NAI members no longer will be allowed under their own rules to deliver targeted content and/or ads to you, which will affect this and other sites, but does not mean you will no longer receive any targeted content and/or ads. Also, if your browsers are configured to reject cookies when you visit this opt-out page, or you subsequently erase your cookies, use a different Device or change web browsers, your NAI opt-out may not, or may no longer, be effective. Additional information is available on the NAI's web site accessible by the above link. You may also opt-out of receiving third-party behavioral ads on sites by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance (“DAA") web site at <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/#completed>. Similar limitations may apply to the DAA opt-out. We are not responsible for effectiveness of, or compliance with, any third-parties' opt-out options or programs. 

Return to policy summary and navigation

**7.** How Do I Change My Information and Communications Preferences?**

You are responsible for maintaining the accuracy of the information you submit to us, such as your contact information provided as part of registration. The Service may allow you to review, correct or update Personal Information you have provided through the Service's registration forms or otherwise, and you may provide registration updates and changes by contacting us [here](https://www.greybox.com/en/support/). European residents should also see Section 3(k) above. If so, we will make good faith efforts to make requested changes in our then active databases as soon as reasonably practicable (but we may retain prior information as business records). With respect to our mobile and other applications (i.e., when we are the application publisher), if any, you can prospectively stop all collection of information by the application by uninstalling the application. You may use the standard uninstall process as may be available as part of your applicable Device or potentially via the appropriate application or app marketplace. Please note that it is not always possible to completely remove or delete all of your information from our databases and that residual data may remain on backup media or for other reasons. Also, if you have made any public postings on the Service such as in forums or blogs, these communications cannot generally be removed. When you edit your Personal Information or change your preferences on the Service, information that you remove may persist internally for Company's administrative purposes. You may cancel or modify our e-mail marketing communications you receive from us by following the instructions contained within our promotional e-mails or in some cases by logging into your Service account and changing your communication preferences. This will not affect subsequent subscriptions and if your opt-out is limited to certain types of e-mails the opt-out will be so limited. If you subscribe to text messages from us, you can terminate a particular text message subscription by reply texting “STOP." Subsequent or different subscriptions will be unaffected. Please note that we reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to your account or use of our Service, such as administrative and service announcements and these transactional account messages may be unaffected if you choose to opt-out from receiving our marketing communications. If you have any questions about the Privacy Policy or practices described in it, you should contact us in the following ways: Postal Mail: **_Grey Box, 1100 Louisiana Street, 52nd Floor, Houston, TX 77002, Attn: Legal Department_** ; By e-mail [www.greybox.com/support/contact/](http://www.greybox.com/support/contact/). 

Return to policy summary and navigation

**8\. What About Transfer of Information to the United States?**

Our Service is operated in the United States and intended for users located in the United States. If you are located outside of the United States, please be aware that information we collect, including Personal Information, will be transferred to, and processed, stored and used in the United States. The data protection laws in the United States may differ from those of the country in which you are located, and your Personal Information may be subject to access requests from governments, courts, or law enforcement in the United States according to laws of the United States. By using the Service or providing us with any information, you consent to the transfer to, and processing, usage, sharing and storage of your information, including Personal Information, in the United States as set forth in this Privacy Policy. 

Return to policy summary and navigation

**9\. What Should Parents Know About Children?**

We understand the importance of protecting children's privacy in the interactive world. We are a general audience service and do not use the Service to knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of thirteen (13) that requires parental notice and consent under the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (“ **COPPA** ") without such parental consent. If you are a child under 13 years of age, you are not permitted to use the Service and should not send any information about yourself to us through the Service.  
In the event that we become aware that we have collected personal information from any child, we will dispose of that information in accordance with COPPA and other applicable laws and regulations. If you are a parent or guardian and you believe that your child under the age of 13 has provided us with personal information without COPPA-required consent, please contact us [here](https://www.greybox.com/en/support/). 

Return to policy summary and navigation

**10\. What About Security?**

We endeavor to incorporate commercially reasonable safeguards to help protect and secure your Personal Information. However, no data transmission over the Internet, mobile networks, wireless transmission or electronic storage of information can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Please note that we cannot ensure the security of any information you transmit to us, and you use our Service and provide us with your information at your own risk. 

Return to policy summary and navigation

**11\. What About Changes to the Privacy Policy?**

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. Any changes will be effective immediately upon the posting of the revised Privacy Policy and your use of our Service indicates your consent to the privacy policy posted at the time of use. However, we will not use your previously collected Personal Information in a manner materially different than represented at the time it was collected without your consent. To the extent any provision of this Privacy Policy is found by a competent tribunal to be invalid or unenforceable, such provision shall be severed to the extent necessary for the remainder to be valid and enforceable. 

Return to policy summary and navigation
